[Music]
what is up everyone money will be Josh
this is strain central and today we are
gonna be doing a product review on the
vivants ambit so this is actually just a
dry herb vaporizer a convection
vaporizer that honestly I'd kind of
considered to be like the budget but
also like one of the more functional
vaporizers so I don't say that with any
kind of a slight like this is the
cheapest vaporizer I've ever found that
is the most functional for its price I
would honestly have to say this is one
of those vapes that kind of puts up with
like my teas the craft DS the Evo's like
all of the top tier vapes that are two
three hundred dollars this thing I'm not
just saying this is like a paid
endorsement I'd really enjoy this thing
for 89 or $79.99 and that's like the
most reasonable price that I've found
for a vape in a long time but I'm
already rambling and I just started the
video so let's actually jump into kind
of like specs and stuff of the actual
unit also random little like side bit of
Avant
most people don't know even how to say
the name but vivant actually means
living in French so most or some people
will translate that as life
but living is technically what that
actually means in French so it's not
just a random name vivant it actually
has like meaning behind it that all
being said let's actually jump into the
specs of the unit so like I said earlier
this is just a drier vaporizer and it
actually is a convection vaporizer as
what they claimed so after playing with
it and using it for a while I'd say
that's a pretty substantiating claim
that being said I'd say it's more of
maybe like an 80/20 or a 9010 hybrid
convection vaporizer just because this
actually does have I haven't actually
been able to confirm if it's stainless
or aluminum but the herb does sit in the
chamber and it does actually have some
direct contact so I consider that
technically conduction that all being
said it's really really really good at
like evenly heating material and and I
unless I'm in the crepeyness super high
heats I have that one almost no actual
combustion so for the actual screen
itself it does actually have a no LED
screen on top here
it's the standard 5 click turn on like
basically every other vape and when it
comes to temperature adjustment you can
adjust from 212 to 446 degrees by a
specific degree so I know for people
that chase Terps that chase flavor that
like specific you know temperatures
that's really awesome
and I've also found that when you kind
of have like entire variability like
this you can pick and find what works
for you it's not just like oh I guess I
have to use the green setting or I have
to use the blue setting or I have to use
the red setting like you can find the
exact temperature that you can kind of
use and honestly vaping different
material you'll find that different
material needs different temperatures so
for me in in units like this the by the
degree variability is really important
and an $80 price point I've never seen
that like anything usually under
probably one hundred and fifty dollars
just has like four basic settings that
they choose and they set so the entire
kind of like variability aspect of this
is really cool to me so the chamber like
I said earlier is I don't know if it's
aluminum or if it's stainless but it's
some kind of a metal and it's about a
half gram you can probably load it a
little bit more that I've honestly found
between like 0.3 and 0.5 is like the
sweet spot for it so battery why is this
thing does actually have a 1500 milliamp
hour battery which they claim will last
for 10 sessions and what a session is is
basically this thing has a 120 second
heat up timer so what that means is
mcsally's power in that like small
amount of time which is actually kind of
a good thing like I was sketched out by
that at first and annoyed me at first
but then I realized that I don't have to
take a 15 second super long draw to
actually get a cloud so the mouthpiece
itself is also really cool because it's
magnetic so you can just like really
quickly pop it off it's a strong magnet
so I haven't found it like popping off
in my pocket or anything annoying like
that but it's a really easy to clean you
can take it entirely apart mouthpiece
that's made of a poly ether ether ketone
or peak for short which is basically
just a food grade plastic
the organic polymer plastic they feel
the things and it's been used since like
the 1980s so it's it's pretty like
well-known as well studied and it's safe
to use and I think the last two specs
that I need to cover are just the actual
charging so it charges with just really
standard microUSB and then it weighs I
think about 3.5 ounces which is just
about a hundred grams so it's not like a
super heavy unit but you still feel like
you have something in your hands and
that all being sell so this is actually
a really really quality well-made
feeling product like some of the cheaper
if you buy just feel super cheap but
because they actually use like quality
plastics yet again it feels like it's a
nice piece and that poly poly
I can't even say polyether ether ketone
is usually really only used in like the
super high-end vapes like yet again the
crafty or their mighty so the fact that
this was used are like a cheap vape a
budget vape that works is it blows my
mind I forgot to turn the heater off so
I haven't [\h__\h] dying in the studio
right now under these lights but let's
actually get to using this guys I
definitely hope you guys are smoking
along that along with long getting those
kinder late play some deep into your
lungs because these are gonna be deep in
to mine it's heating right now it's
getting ready to go
but uh choose guys I guess we'll get
ourselves a nice hit
[Music]
and that was not a combusted hit that's
the best part about this is you can get
hits that almost kind of look like
clouds but are still vapor and don't
combust your material like all those
things combined or what kind of blown
any weight with this so like I said you
only get two minutes so it's a pretty
quick little session that being said
your first couple of rips like actually
deliver that vape to you and it's not
like you're just sitting there like is
this thing gonna work am I gonna need
anything out of this and usually babes
that produce like this you're seeing
them almost immediately combust your
bowl all your weeds burnt it's not
actually vaporizing so very impressive
honestly I can say this not like I said
is like earlier not just as and you can
also increase the session time if you
really want to by just pressing the
button twice it adds another 30 seconds
on to your session turn this thing off
you just hold the button to turn it off
and then it stops heating your sessions
done so it's super super super easy to
use this is like the perfect beginner
vape because some of the raves I've used
especially like the Magic Flight box the
learning curve is just it takes months
to figure out headaches they hit it
perfectly whereas this you can hit
perfectly almost every time so I've
found a lot of like I'm legitimately
impressed I have a closet full of
vaporizers that I never touch I
actually found myself reaching for this
and like normal sessions so it's it's
legitimately impressive so after like
actually emptying us out and dumping the
material out on the table this is
entirely just vaporized material there's
no blackening there's no combustion and
honestly I'm vaping pretty high so I
guess we basically just break down pros
and cons now even though I almost kind
of feel like this entire video has
basically just been like a pro reasons
why I actually enjoy this vaporizer but
I have found some cons that I will
obviously throw in can throw in all the
time and they're very minor but they're
improvements that can really easily be
made so and honestly one of them can be
improved by something they sell so my
first big technical con is the fact that
if you hit this like three sessions the
mouthpiece does heat up it does get kind
of hot it's a little bit annoying that
being said they actually have a water
pipe attachment and I think they're
making other mouthpieces so I don't
think that's gonna be an issue in the
future and then I think my second con
would probably just be charged time I
feel like this could hold a little bit
more of a charge
realistically you only get if you're
using it consistently a day's worth of
use out of it so it doesn't have a 1500
milliamp hour battery which I don't must
expect to hold a little bit more of
charge that being said I is some easy
fix and version to bigger battery and
that's about all you really need maybe a
mouthpiece that's a little bit bigger to
kind of make a bigger vapor pathway and
cool that smoke down a little bit but
that's really all I got for cons so I
genuinely enjoy this unit I feel like I
haven't like ranted and raved about a
vape like this in a long time so thank
you very much for Vaughn for actually
sending this on over my way I'm gonna go
ahead and take one more big ol rip off
this boy and call this an episode so I
definitely hope every single one of you
is having yourself an awesome day I
definitely hope if shit's going rough
that you find you find the power to push
through it you find the power to get
some [\h__\h] done and you realize that you
are who you can be your good person you
just have to you know work towards that
good person so cheers guys
my camera would die mid final hit so
cheers guys finally hit now stay
positive stay medicated peace guys